Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben &J's flavors, but lower in
calories and higher in protein. This is
New York Super Fudge Chunk. Let me show
you how to make it. This is a chocolate
base. So, we're using a chocolate
protein shake, some cocoa powder, salt,
sweetener, zantham gum. We're just going
to blend that all up and throw it in the
freezer for at least 16 hours. Once it's
completely frozen through, you can take
it out and run it under hot water for
about a minute and throw it in your
creamy on the light ice cream setting.
You're probably going to need one or two
respins. Just be wary so when it comes
out powdery, you don't think you messed
up the recipe. Now for mixins, we are
using walnuts, pecans, dark chocolate,
white chocolate, and chocolate covered
almonds. A whole slew of mixins. All you
need to do with these is chop them up so
they're approximately the same size. I
used a slap chop, which I put in a video
a couple weeks ago, and you guys all
made fun of me for using it, but this is
literally the only reason that it
exists. So, I'm going to use it when I
can. Find a way to chop them all up,
throw them on top, and mix them in by
hand.